webmasterbond.com 2011-12-11

# Privacy Policy | WebmasterBond

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site: you will be asked to enter your name and e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously and use our free tools without registering.

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes, we use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits. (Cookies are small files that a site transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and remember certain information.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

Users who create an account on our site can change their information anytime by logging in and then clicking 'My Dashboard' at the top-right of any page.

### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act). Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

### Terms and Conditions

For information on the policies specific to our AdServer application, visit these links:

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we change our privacy policy, those changes will be post on this page. The modification date below indicates the last time this policy was updated:

This policy was last modified on **August 1, 2011**

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at: [WebmasterBond Support](mailto:support@webmasterbond.com).

This policy is powered by Trust Guard PCI compliant security scanning.
